Marcus Quoyeser

sim0n@protonmail.com

Writing

•Intro

I have been a writer for most of my life, in one way or another. For the past five years I have dedicated my almost non-limited time to honing in my skills. I took time off school, work, and responsibility to travel. I lived in Vienna, Austria for a time, learning a bit about web application development at a startup. After this I spent a few months in Stavropol, Russia, in the heart of the North Caucasus region. It was a unique trip, and I grew as a writer.

•Professional

Copywriting— I have done various amounts of freelance copywriting over the past couple of years. I have worked on articles for a defunct elopement blog, written as a ghost writer on product reviews, developed content for a website on short stories, and I have done a few articles that dealt with the topic of clear and concise writing.

Creative

Fiction— I am in the process of finishing up an epic fantasy novel. It has hints of science fiction and themes of growth, pain, and friendship. I have spent ample time editing this piece, and I consider my knowledge of editing to be quite competent. I also type really, really fast and make few errors.

•Languages

```
Programming— learning Python, some Javascript
Scripting— Bash, Python, learning Perl
Markup— HTML, CSS, IATFX, Markdown
```

General

•Traits

I am empathetic, compassionate, focused, and communicative. I love knowledge almost as much as I love experience and adventure.

•Second Languages

Can speak— Native English speaker, A2 level Russian (and learning)

Education

•St. Thomas More High School - 2004-2008

Graduated with high school diploma.

•University of Louisiana at Lafayette - 2008+

I studied Creative Writing on and off when I could afford it, but I am not yet finished.

Work Experience

•Quoyeser, Inc. - 2005-2016

Printshop— I was in charge of running multiple digital printing machines and general warehouse and printshop management. I did hardware and software troubleshooting as was needed, and I am very comfortable in both areas.

•Self-Employed - 2015-Present

Content Writer— I work from home, coffee shops, or anywhere with a WiFi connection as a freelance writer. I have done work as a ghostwriter and content writer.

•Community Coffee - 11/2009-05/2010

Lead Barista— I was a Lead Barista whose duties were to prepare fresh and delicious coffee.

Other

•Music

I make electronic music! soundcloud.com/mopfunk